[
  {
    "front": "accomplice",
    "back": "đồng loã, tòng phạm",
    "topic": "Con người"
  },
  {
    "front": "format",
    "back": "định dạng",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "dog",
    "back": "con chó",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "cat",
    "back": "con mèo",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "owl",
    "back": "con cú",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "puppy",
    "back": "chó con",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "kitten",
    "back": "mèo con",
    "topic": "Động vật"
  },
  {
    "front": "library",
    "back": "thư viện",
    "topic": "Trường học"
  },
  {
    "front": "school",
    "back": "trường học",
    "topic": "Trường học"
  },
  {
    "front": "project",
    "back": "dự án",
    "topic": "Công việc"
  }
]